<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Best 10 Telescopes in 2019</string>

    <string name="overview">
In choosing the best telescopes, you should consider your level of expertise. There are numerous choices out there and selecting the best one can be mind-boggling especially if you only have a limited budget. Most people think that getting a starter telescope costs a lot. In reality, there is a legion of options out there which only costs below $250. However, it is also essential that it is made of high-quality optics and has a firm mounting in order to have an enjoyable experience. Keep in mind that you should choose a model that is very easy and convenient to use. Additionally, it should also be portable.
    </string>

    <string name="bt1">
Celestron NexStar SE is chosen as the best telescope of the year for four consecutive years. It has the best technological features, aperture, and value. It is also very portable to use. Regardless, if you are a first time or you want to upgrade your current telescope, Celestron NexStar SE is the best choice.\n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    This is one of the best telescopes since it uses the Schmidt-Cassegrain or Maksutov-Cassegrain \n optical system. It allows you to broaden your aperture from four inches to eight inches. \n
◾    The Star Bright XLT optical coatings offer you excellent brightness and clearness. \n
◾    The Sky Align Technology allows you to locate several celestial objects by merely pointing 3 \n objects in the sky.
◾    You can choose to add the SkyQ Link 2 Wifi Module. With this module, you can make use of \n your smartphone is managing your telescope. \n
◾    The telescope can align on its own with the use of Star Sense Auto Align. \n

</string>

    <string name="bt2">
Telescope

Celestron CPC Deluxe HD Series are considered as the best telescopes for navigation. It is very easy to set up. It comes with a GPS. All you have to do is turn on the telescope and it will automatically recognize the time, date, latitude and longitude. Just point it at the center of 3 objects and you can instantly locate numerous celestial objects in the sky. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    Deluxe HD models come with enhanced tracking accuracy. \n
◾    You can guarantee its stability because of its dual form arm mount. \n
◾    The EdgeHD of Celestron has superb clarity. \n

</string>

    <string name="bt3">
Celestron AstroMaster 114EQ is one of the best telescopes for beginners. A lot of people are using this telescope in viewing the universe. This is due to its large primary mirror. It is the perfect telescope for first timers since it has a very simple design. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    This telescope has an excellent light gathering ability to let you see different celestial objects clearly. \n
◾    The equatorial mount is very useful for first timers. It can track the celestial objects accurately even if it moves. \n
◾    Celestron AstroMaster 114EQ is very affordable since it only costs below $200. \n
◾    It comes with everything you need including the tripod, mount, accessories and of course the telescope. \n
◾    Download Celestron’s stargazing app, SkyPortal to learn more about various celestial objects. \n

</string>

    <string name="bt4">
If you require a larger telescope then the best option is the Sky-Watcher GoTo Collapsible Dobsonian. There are different sizes to choose from. The bigger the size, the more details you can see. Storing is not a problem since it can be disassembled. This is perfect if you are transporting it from one place to another. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    The GOTo technology and the large aperture are very useful for astronomy enthusiasts. \n
◾    The SynScan hand control is very easy to use. \n
◾    The telescope remains aligned regardless if you swing it. \n

</string>

    <string name="bt5">
Let your kids discover the universe with Vixen Space Eye 50mm Telescope. This is one of the best telescopes for kids. It is very easy to use, making it perfect for kids. This telescope only weighs 6.2 lbs so your children can install it on their own. It comes with a 50mm refractor which can be used for gazing at the planets and the moon. You can easily make any adjustments through its altazimuth. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    It includes two eyepieces. \n
◾    The finderscope is very helpful if your children want to explore the night sky. \n

</string>


    <string name="bt6">
Celestron NexStar 127 SLT might be a bit expensive, however, it definitely is one of the best telescopes for beginners. This telescope is computerized, this means that you can easily locate celestial objects in the sky. A lot of astronomy enthusiasts get easily frustrated if they can’t find any celestial objects after a couple of hours. With this computerized telescope, they won’t get discouraged anymore. Even amateurs can get the chance to watch the stars instantly. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    It’s quality and price are just perfect. \n

</string>


    <string name="bt7">
This telescope is the most expensive on our list, however, it’s also the best rated. It has a superior image quality. Orion 8945 can be used by any stargazers of different levels. If you want to attach a camera to the telescope then you should purchase an additional attachment. It weighs more or less 40 lbs. after it is assembled. It is a little bit heavier if you want to transfer it to another location. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    It comes with the Starry Night astronomy software which is perfect for beginners. \n
◾    This is the best telescope for those who love to watch celestial objects that do not fade too quickly. \n
◾    Orion 8945 can last for years. \n

</string>


    <string name="bt8">
If you have a tight budget then Celestron 127EQ PowerSeeker Telescope is the best option for you. This is also one of the best telescopes for kids. It is very easy to set up and it does not require any tools. It gives you 300x magnification. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    It comes with two types of eyepieces. \n
◾    This telescope includes TheSkyX software where you can learn a lot of things about celestial objects. \n
◾    This is the best choice for those who are looking for cheap telescopes. \n

</string>


    <string name="bt9">
At first glance, you can quickly tell that this telescope is durably built. You can guarantee that this telescope can last for years. You can easily transfer it from one place to another since it is mounted on wheels. The only downside of this telescope is that it does not stand too tall. This means that huge people have to bend over in order to look through the telescope. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    It comes with TheSkyX software to help you in exploring the universe. \n
◾    Orion 10014 is very portable. It is your best companion while you travel. \n
◾    This is a mid-range telescope and has a reasonable price. If you want to enjoy the amazing view of the sky but don’t want to pay more then this is the best telescope for you. \n


</string>


    <string name="bt10">

Celestron 70mm Travel Scope is the cheapest and the smallest telescope on the list. It is a fact that great things come in small packages. And this telescope is the proof of that. This telescope is very convenient and portable. It is ideal for people who want to travel to places where they can enjoy a vast view of the sky. Obviously, if you travel you don’t want to bring those bulky devices with you, this isn’t practical. What this telescope lacks are power and size. \n\n

Features: \n\n

◾    This telescope includes a bag and a tripod. \n
◾    It is very easy to set up so you can start star gazing right away. \n
◾    This can make a great gift for your kids who are interested in astronomy. \n

</string>


</resources>
